#### **NATHAN BERGER**

3434 Pinemont Dr, Douglasville, GA 30135 Contact: 7578467339 nberger101@gmail.com

### Summary

Seasoned network and systems technician turned web developer with experience in direct customer support, network hardware configuration and maintenance, server installation and management, and functional programming. Efficient communicator with 4 years experience with troubleshooting complex network and desktop issues in numerous Joint military exercises, active warfighting environments, and healthcare settings. Duties included working collaboratively with clients, coworkers, implementation consultants, and resources across the organization to streamline company workflows and meet customer needs.

### Skills

- IP protocols and WAN technologies
- Virtualization solutions
- Hardware and software support
- Cisco iOS
- HTML, CSS, Git, UNIX
- Fundamental Javascript

- Excellent communication skills
- Strong troubleshooting experience
- Service oriented personality
- Team player
- Strong organizational skills
- MS Windows, Server, Office

# **Related Work History**

### United States Air Force, Cyber Transport Specialist, 2013 - 2014

- Provide network and end user support in active military exercises
- Build and maintain working knowledge of strict information assurance practices
- Develop and translate strong leadership skills into action oriented service
- Manage large inventory of high value transmission equipment

### Greenway Health, Technical Support, 2014 - 2015

- Direct communication with end users and various support staff
- Handle wide range of technical issues through mitigation or escalation
- Administrative use of Salesforce

### MAG Aerospace, Network Systems Analyst, 2015 - 2019

- Day to day maintenance of backbone networking equipment
- 24/7 support of network, system, and end user workflows
- Maintain detailed logging of all incidents and mitigation techniques used
- · Active monitoring of NIPRNet, SIPRNet, JWICS, VOIP systems
- Maintenance of live video encoding and decoding equipment

# Cloud Microphones, Warehouse Associate and Product Assembly, 2020 - 2023

- Duties included daily product inspection and assembly, quality assurance, and packing
- Maintained warehouse upkeep, organization, and safety per OSHA guidelines
- Assisted in order preparation, packaging and shipping in high volumes

# **Education**

- Past Certifications: CCNA Routing and Switching, CompTIA A+/Sec+/Net+
- Rithm School Immersive Software Engineering Program (in progress)